Finding Aid to the Georgia O'Keeffe Photographs, 1882-1974, undated MS.37
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
Georgia O'Keeffe Photographs
1882-1974, undated
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
MS.37
56
2.88 Linear Feet
This collection includes photographic material relating to Georgia O'Keeffe and her properties dating from 1908 to c. 1964. In addition to photographs there are clippings, prints, correspondence, printed material, and a watercolor and graphite drawing.
Arrangement of Collection
Series arrangement is by general media type.
Biographical and Historical Note
Georgia O'Keeffe was one of the most photographed women of the twentieth century. She actively participated in the creation of her own dramatic image, beginning in 1918, with the series of more than 300 photographs created by Alfred Stieglitz. After Stieglitz's death and her move to the remote village of Abiquiu in New Mexico, important portrait photographers followed her west to picture her at home and in her studio.
In 2006, The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation transferred O'Keeffe's personal photograph collection to the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum. This collection consists of both fine art photography and a wide range of archival photographic materials such as copy prints, negatives, contact sheets, documentary photographs, and personal snap shots. The photographic archive forms an invaluable record of O'Keeffe's life in art, a creative practice that spanned the twentieth century and the rise of American Modernism.
The photographs in this collection, MS.37, were originally in O'Keeffe's possession and given to James Johnson Sweeney when he was working on a book about her, which was never published.
James Johnson Sweeney (1900-1986) was an art curator, critic, historian, and museum director. Sweeney was a curator for the Museum of Modern Art from 1935 to 1946 and the director of the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, from 1952 to 1960. Sweeney was appointed director of the Museum of Fine Arts in Houston in 1961 where he stayed for several years. Sweeney was the curator of O'Keeffe's 1946 retrospective at the Museum of Modern Art and consulted her on aspects of her career.
Scope and Content Note
The collection comprises almost 200 photographs, including copy prints, film, contact sheets, documentary photographs, and personal snap shots, all relating to the life and work of Georgia O'Keeffe. Many photographs are of O'Keeffe or her New Mexico properties.
Part of this collection was accessioned into the Museum's art collection, including fine art photography by such artists as Alfred Stieglitz, Ansel Adams, Laura Gilpin, Todd Webb, and Philip Halsman. Those photographs share an accession number scheme beginning with 2014.03.
The collection also contains a limited amount of correspondence, ephemera, clippings, popular prints, and one watercolor and graphite work by an unknown individual.
Related Materials
Part of this collection was accessioned into the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum's art collection. Those photographs share a similar accession number, 2014.03. There are similar or related photographs in various Georgia O'Keeffe Museum archival collections.
Access Restrictions
The collection is open to the public for research purposes.
This collection is the physical property of the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum. The Museum holds literary rights only for material created by Museum personnel or given to the Museum with such rights specifically assigned. The collection is subject to all copyright laws. The researcher assumes full responsibility for observing all copyright, property, and libel laws as they apply. Contact the Archivist for further copyright and publication information as it pertains to this collection.
Acquisition Information
This collection was purchased by Georgia O'Keeffe Museum in 2014.
Correspondence; Drawings; Clippings; Prints; Photographs
- Photographs, circa 1908-1964, undated; 1; 2938
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.106; 3136; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2 inches (Box 1)
    Copyright Estate of George Daniell
    Photographs; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.107; 3135; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 1.875 x 2 inches (Box 1)
    Photographs
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.108; 3134; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 1.875 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.109; 3133; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2 x 1.875 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.110; 3132; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2 x 1.875 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.111; 3131; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 1.875 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.112; 3130; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 1.625 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe profile silhouette, 1952; 2014.3.113; 3129; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe silhouette with plants, 1952; 2014.3.114; 3128; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.125 x 1.5 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with Pancho, Abiquiu patio, 1952; 2014.3.115; 3127; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, outside Abiquiu studio, 1952; 2014.3.116; 3126; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with unidentified man in Abiquiu garden, 1952; 2014.3.117; 3125; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.125 x 1.875 inches (Box 1)
  - Two unidentified people in Abiquiu garden, 1952; 2014.3.118; 3124; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 1.875 inches (Box 1)
  - Abiquiu studio window, 1952; 2014.3.119; 3123; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Abiquiu studio window and easel, 1952; 2014.3.120; 3122; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2.25 inches (Box 1)
  - Abiquiu studio window and easel, 1952; 2014.3.121; 3121; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2 x 2.25 inches (Box 1)
  - Silhouetted plants in Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu bedroom window, 1952; 2014.3.122; 3120; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2.125 inches (Box 1)
  - Plants in sitting room window, 1952; 2014.3.123; 3119; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.125 x 1.625 inches (Box 1)
  - Plants in window, 1952; 2014.3.124; 3118; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Plants in window, 1952; 2014.3.125; 3117; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Cubic Feet Gelatin silver print 2 x 1.75 inches (Box 1)
  - Pancho, Abiquiu patio, 1952; 2014.3.126; 3116; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Pancho, Abiquiu patio, 1952; 2014.3.127; 3115; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.125 x 2.25 inches (Box 1)
  - Abiquiu exterior, 1952; 2014.3.128; 3114; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.125 x 2.25 inches (Box 1)
  - Adobe gardens looking north, 1952; 2014.3.129; 3113; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.125 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - Abiquiu house gate looking east, 1952; 2014.3.130; 3112; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2.125 inches (Box 1)
  - Abiquiu house gate looking east, 1952; 2014.3.131; 3111; Daniell, George, 1911-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 2.25 x 2.25 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, 1966; 2014.3.133; 3110; Looney, Ralph, 1924-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 10 x 8 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, 1966; 2014.3.134; 3109; Looney, Ralph, 1924-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 10 x 8 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe [wearing white head scarf], 1964-06; 2014.3.135; 3108; Marcus, Stanley, 1905-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 10 x 8 inches (Box 1)
    Copyright Stanley Marcus
    General
    Letter from Stanley Marcus to Georgia O'Keeffe regarding sending the photo to O'Keeffe taken at the June 1964 opening of the Deere and Co. Administrative Center in Moline, Illinois where Alexander Girard designed a three dimensional mural.
  - Georgia O'Keeffe [wearing white head scarf], 1964-06; 2014.3.136; 3107; Marcus, Stanley, 1905-2002; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 10 x 8 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Carl Van Vechten, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.137; 3106; Mauriber, Saul, 1915-2003; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 5 x 7 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Carl Van Vechten, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.138; 3105; Mauriber, Saul, 1915-2003; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 4.5 x 7 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Carl Van Vechten, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.139; 3104; Mauriber, Saul, 1915-2003; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 5 x 7 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Christopher Isherwood at Ghost Ranch, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.153; 3103; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7 x 4.875 inches (Box 1)
    Copyright The Van Vechten Trust
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Christopher Isherwood at Ghost Ranch, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.154; 3102; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7 x 4.875 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Christopher Isherwood at Ghost Ranch, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.155; 3101; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7 x 4.5 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Christopher Isherwood at Ghost Ranch, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.156; 3100; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 6.75 x 4.5 inches (Box 1)
  - Ghost Ranch, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.157; 3099; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 4.75 x 7 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch house, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.158; 3098; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 4.625 x 7 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch house, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.159; 3097; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 5 x 7 inches (Box 1)
  - Ghost Ranch, 1950-08-16; 2014.3.160; 3096; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 4.75 x 7 inches (Box 1)
  - Church, 1950-08-17; 2014.3.161; 3095; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7 x 4.75 inches (Box 1)
  - The Carl Van Vechten Gallery, Fisk University, 1955-05-30; 2014.3.162; 3094; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 9.875 x 6.625 inches (Box 1)
  - The Carl Van Vechten Gallery, Fisk University, 1955-05-30; 2014.3.163; 3093; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 9.25 x 6.25 inches (Box 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.164; 3092; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
    Copyright Estate of Todd Webb
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.165; 3091; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.166; 3090; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.167; 3089; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 in (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.168; 3088; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.169; 3087; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.170; 3086; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.171; 3085; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.172; 3084; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.173; 3083; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.174; 3082; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.175; 3081; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.176; 3080; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.177; 3079; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.178; 3078; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, Interior Gallery View, 1946; 2014.3.179; 3077; Webb, Todd, 1905-2000; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.625 x 9.625 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Reproduction of pelvis painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.180; 3076; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 9.5 x 7.375 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of pelvis painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.181; 3075; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 7.75 x 9.75 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of pelvis painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.182; 3074; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 9.5 x 7.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of Brown and Tan Leaves (CR0641) by Georgia O'Keeffe [mounted on Stieglitz exhibition announcement for 'Georgia O'Keeffe New Paintings', 1941], undated; 2014.3.183; 3073; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 9.375 x 7.125 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of Georgia O'Keeffe - Hands by Alfred Stieglitz, undated; 2014.3.184; 3072; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Cubic Feet Copy print 9.25 x 7.25 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of Georgia O'Keeffe - Hands by Alfred Stieglitz, undated; 2014.3.185; 3071; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 7.25 x 9.25 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of Georgia O'Keeffe - Hands by Alfred Stieglitz, undated; 2014.3.186; 3070; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 9.375 x 7 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of Georgia O'Keeffe - Hands and Thimble by Alfred Stieglitz, undated; 2014.3.187; 3069; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 7.25 x 9.25 inches (Oversize 1)
  - Reproduction of Georgia O'Keeffe [Wearing Dark Vest with Round Gold Brooch] by Alfred Stieglitz, undated; 2014.3.188; 3068; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 9.25 x 7.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Reproduction of Georgia O'Keeffe [Wearing Hat, Carrying Woven Shoulder Bag, and Carrying Woven Tray] by Alfred Stieglitz, undated; 2014.3.189; 3067; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; Peter A. Juley & Son; 1 Linear Feet Copy print 9.25 x 7.25 inches (Box 2)
  - Fashion photograph of model standing in front of pelvis painting [probably at Georgia O'Keeffe exhibit at An American Place for Vogue], circa 1945; 2014.3.190; 3066; Reynal, Kay Bell, 1905-1977; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 13.375 x 10.5 inches (Oversize 1)
    Copyright National Portrait Gallery
  - Woman with baby, undated; 2014.3.191; 3065; Borsig, Tet Arnold von, 1899-1972; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5 x 7 inches (Box 2)
  - Woman with baby, undated; 2014.3.192; 3064; Borsig, Tet Arnold von, 1899-1972; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 7 x 5 inches (Box 2)
  - Golden Gate Bridge, undated; 2014.3.193; 3063; Borsig, Tet Arnold von, 1899-1972; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 8 x 10 inches (Box 2)
  - Cityscape (San Francisco), undated; 2014.3.194; 3062; Borsig, Tet Arnold von, 1899-1972; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 8 x 10 inches (Box 2)
  - Lord and Taylor window display, "Lord and Taylor salutes Women at Work", undated; 2014.3.195; 3061; Roehl, Virginia; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 10 x 8 inches (Box 2)
  - Wood and stone abstraction, circa 1962; 2014.3.196; 3060; Saunders, Gene; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4 x 5.75 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with cat, undated; 2014.3.197; 3059; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.5 x 3.125 inches (Box 2)
    Copyright Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in Hawaii, undated; 2014.3.198; 3058; Stein, Harold; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.75 x 3 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe at University of Virginia, circa 1915; 2014.3.199; 3057; Holsinger's Studio (Charlottesville, Va.); 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph; postcard 5.5 x 3.5 inches (Box 2)
    Copyright Holsinger Studio
  - Abiquiu house, bedroom, 1960; 2014.3.200; 3056; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints Diffusion transfer print 7.5 x 4.25 inches (Box 2)
    Copyright Amon Carter Museum of American Art
  - Georgia O'Keeffe [with mounted bird], circa 1941; 2014.3.201; 3055; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin sliver 10 x 8 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe [with mounted bird], circa 1941; 2014.3.202; 3054; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Cibachrome 8.75 x 6 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and unidentified woman at Dr. Barnes, undated; 2014.3.203; 3053; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 8 x 10 inches (Box 2)
  - Portrait of unidentified baby, undated; 2014.3.204; 3052; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 6.375 x 4.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and friends at picnic, undated; 2014.3.205; 3051; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5 x 5 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and chow, undated; 2014.3.206; 3050; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5.5 x 4.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in profile, undated; 2014.3.207; 3049; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 7 x 5.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in front of ladder, undated; 2014.3.208; 3048; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 3.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in front of ladder, undated; 2014.3.209; 3047; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 3.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.210; 3046; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
    Copyright Josephine B. Marks
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.211; 3045; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.212; 3044; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in shawl at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.213; 3043; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in shawl at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.214; 3042; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in shawl at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.215; 3041; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in shawl at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.216; 3040; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in shawl at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.217; 3039; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in shawl at Lake George, circa 1938; 2014.3.218; 3038; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.5 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - Possibly Alfred Stieglitz as young man, undated; 2014.3.219; 3037; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 7.5 x 5.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Possibly Alfred Stieglitz as young man, undated; 2014.3.220; 3036; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7.5 x 5.5 inches (Box 2)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.221; 3035; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 4.125 x 3 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.222; 3034; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 4 x 3.125 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.223; 3033; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 4.125 x 3.375 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.224; 3032; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 4.25 x 3.125 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with cat and dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.225; 3031; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 3.75 x 2.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.226; 3030; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 4.25 x 2.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Unidentified woman with dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.227; 3029; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 3.875 x 2.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe carrying clothing, undated; 2014.3.228; 3028; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 4 x 3.75 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in Texas, circa 1916-1918; 2014.3.229; 3027; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 6.875 x 4.25 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in Texas, circa 1916-1918; 2014.3.230; 3026; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 6.25 x 3.875 inches (Box 3)
  - Ghost Ranch, 1950-05-16; 2014.3.231; 3025; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 3 x 6.875 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in Texas, circa 1916-1918; 2014.3.232; 3024; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5.375 x 3.25 inches (Box 3)